Have you ever heard about that
the cliff of a snow mountain
once fascinated numerous people?
Legend has it that,
there were treasures at the peak
but also there was a bottomless chasm hidden over there.
The smart, the fool
and the kind people,
all are familiar to you.
On the mountainside, on the cliff,
on the cloud,
and in the human world,
snowflakes are drifting profusely and disorderly.
Joy of Life Season 1
Episode 11
That day,
there were many guests.
The maidservant you're looking for
might not be from my mansion.
If so,
it won't be easy to find her.
What if I visit all the families
one by one?
I'm afraid you'll probably be kicked out.
Maybe we should stop.
Actually, there's still another way.
But it's much worse.
Even worse?
Sister, can I go home?
Ruoruo,
do you know Lin Wan'er?
I've met her several times and talked a few words.
Where does she live?
Sick with tuberculosis,
she stays in an imperial residence all the year round.
She is the key to this marriage.
Come on! Let's go to the imperial residence.
Are you going to
kill her?
Come with me.
You don't go inside?
I don't.
They are crazy!
Lady Ruoruo, wait a moment.
I will go and report.
Thank you.
Fan Ruoruo has gone to the imperial residence,
saying she has brought a famous doctor
to see Wan'er.
Auntie, why are you smiling so weirdly?
That doctor
is Fan Xian.
They're not married yet. How can they meet in private?
I heard that Fan Xian is the student of Fei Jie.
Those who are good at using poison are also doctors.
Let them see Wan'er.
Auntie,
aren't you against
the marriage all the time?
Fan Xian just left Prince Jing's mansion,
saying that he wants to find a maidservant.
A drumstick girl.
You heard about it?
A little bird told me.
Wan'er doesn't want to marry him.
Nor does Fan Xian.
The only person insist on them getting married
is His Majesty.
If Wan'er detests
or even hates Fan Xian,
then His Majesty might reconsider it.
I see.
By pretending to be a doctor,
Fan Xian wants to piss Wan'er,
so as to ruin the marriage.
In this sense,
I hope he can succeed.
Do you think he can see Lin Wan'er?
A patient suffers from a long illness
certainly wants to see a famous doctor.
Choosing a maidservant
over a princess,
it's not worth it.
Indeed.
In this city,
only he will make such a choice.
Second Young Master!
=Lin Gong, the second son of Nanqing Prime Minister Lin Ruofu=
Fan Sizhe.
You must be Fan Xian!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Lady Ruoruo and doctor,
please follow me to see the princess.
Lustful, aggressive, mischievous and ignorant as he is,
Wan'er will never marry
your incorrigible brother.
Tell Fan Xian.
If he doesn't give up,
this is what he'll become.
Who's that?
Do you know who Lin Wan'er is?
She's the bastard daughter of the Princess Royal.
Her birth father
is the current Prime Minister Lin Ruofu.
I've also heard that.
The Prime Minister has two sons.
That's Lin Gong,
the Second Young Master of
the Lin mansion.
So he's the second brother of Lin Wan'er.
Judged from his attitude,
he doesn't seem to like Fan Xian.
That's understandable.
If I were him, I wouldn't like Fan Xian, either.
Lin Gong
cares for Lin Wan'er
since childhood.
If I were in his shoes,
I wouldn't want my sister
to marry such a troublemaker.
Just think about all the troubles Fan Xian has caused
since he arrived in the capital city.
To be honest.
If it weren't for the strict rules of the Lin family,
short-tempered as he is,
he might have rushed into
our mansion long ago.
I've made my point.
Just leave!
Second Young Master, I've brought
a great doctor
to see Wan'er today.
Wan'er has got tuberculosis.
So many famous doctors failed to offer a solution.
Young as he is,
how dare you call him great?
What are you doing?
Go away!
Three!
Guards!
Kick this fraudulent quack
out!
Two!
Ridiculous!
One!
I was right!
His disease...
You... you...
What did you do to me?
Just let me save him first!
His disease
can't be delayed.
His disease...
Your disease has been hidden
for a long time.
Luckily, you meet me today.
It can produce an excruciating pain in the chest.
Once broke out, it can't be delayed.
Or you'll die.
Take this pill right away!
Young Master, if you don't take it,
you'll die.
It's so effective!
What's the name of the disease?
It's called Why Giving Up.
What does it mean?
It means the disease is tricky.
Normally, the cause of the disease can't be figured out.
And eventually, the patient has to abandon treatment.
Why are you still here! Get out!
Yes!
I was wrong.
Master, you're really a great doctor!
Will you forgive my ignorance
and see my sister?
As doctors, we should be benevolent. Just lead the way.
I drugged him.
Second Young Master,
Lady Wan'er has lied down
as you commanded.
Master, sorry for this.
She's unmarried after all.
It's improper for her to show her face.
Master, please.
I'm Fan Xian.
I'm here to see
what my future wife
looks like!
I'm most certain that
by making such a fuss today,
you'll have to let me cancel the marriage!
Fan Xian!
Master.
I'm thinking about the disease.
I'll feel her pulse first.
I'm so sorry.
I'm also doing this for your benefit.
Master, sorry to trouble you.
Who... who are you?
Who is your Young Master?
Master, is there anything wrong?
To treat the disease, a guiding drug is needed.
What is it?
A greasy drumstick under the censer table
in the side palace hall of the Qing Temple.
Such a weird guiding drug.
Why are they still inside?
Lin Gong is inside, and so does Fan Xian.
Will they get into a fight
inside?
What's so good
about girls?
They are talkative and troublesome.
To me,
I might as well count the money!
You're still young.
I'm not!
Besides,
it's not relevant.
Why not have a try?
Try talking to a girl?
That one seems nice.
Should I have a try?
She's good.
Lady, wait a moment!
Would you like to
play Pai Gow with me?
Who are you?
I'm the son of Earl Sinan.
Fan Xian?!
If I were Fan Xian,
will you play Pai Gow with me?
Nothing to look at! Let's go!
Girls are horrible!
What are you doing?
I'm seeing the patient.
Don't you need to feel her pulse?
Watching her face will do.
What do you get?
Does she often cough?
Right!
Does she pine away day by day?
Does she often sweat?
Right!
Does she often feel a hot flush?
Do you figure that out simply by watching her face?
Has she coughed blood?
Yes, she has.
What's wrong with her?
I've confirmed the case.
It's tuberculosis.
We've already know that.
No need for you to tell us!
It can be treated as long as I know her conditions.
Really?
What does she eat?
We've paid attention to that.
No meat and fish. Keep it plain and simple.
You're risking her life.
How is that?
Tuberculosis is a chronic wasting disease.
She really needs to eat meat and fish.
If she seldom eats meat and fish,
she'll grow weak gradually.
Food such as drumsticks
can definitely be served more often.
I'm worried by eating meat,
I'll feel nauseated.
It's fine.
After vomiting several times, you'll just get used to it.
Is that OK?
I'll write a prescription for her later.
In addition,
open that window
more often.
She needs to breathe the fresh air.
Whether it should be closed or not at night,
it's up to the lady.
After all,
you have to prevent others from entering your room at night.
Second Young Master, see you later.
Lady Ruoruo,
the doctor is really talented.
Our family
really owes you this time.
But my mind has not changed.
I won't let your brother
marry Wan'er.
Because Wan'er already has someone
in her heart.
-Who? -What?
It must be Guo Baokun,
son of the Minister of the Board of Rites,
who serves as the imperial compiler.
Guo Bao...
Second Young Master, see you.
Guo Baokun?!
How could it be Guo Baokun?
Guo Baokun?
Second Young Master,
who's that?
A famous doctor invited by Ruoruo.
He's really good.
Why did you just stand there and watch me get kicked?
You're a swordsman after all.
She just
kicked me suddenly!
Why don't you help me?
Your brother is the one who pays me money,
not you.
Then you've done nothing wrong.
Finally, you're out.
How could it be Guo Baokun?!
It's too dramatic!
Why is Guo Baokun involved?
She spat blood?
Just ask her
about it.
Don't you have a date with her tonight?
Sister,
a date with whom?
Lady Drumstick.
It's all set. They'll meet through a window.
Tidy up the room.
Yes.
I've heard that Fan Xian wants to cancel the marriage.
Fan Xian is so rude!
Do be relieved.
I won't let you marry
a vulgar man like him.
Dad is also to blame for this.
Powerful as he is,
he can turn down
the Fan family directly,
but he actually refuses to do it.
After all, I'm not a member of the Lin family.
Dad can't intervene.
How come you are not a member?
You're my younger sister.
You've been treated unfairly for so long.
You deserve to have
a satisfied marriage.
Rest assured.
If dad doesn't handle this, I will.
Haven't you been always saying that
you want to marry for love?
I'll make sure you do!
Whoever you like,
I'll get him for you even by force.
But the marriage is granted by His Majesty.
Our family has pledged loyalty to His Majesty.
But that doesn't mean girls of our family
should marry anyone chosen by His Majesty.
If we're pushed too hard,
we can defy the imperial order at the worst.
Brother, I know
you care about me.
It's so nice to have an elder brother!
Wan'er, let Ling'er keep you company.
Have some girl talks.
No need to worry about anything else.
But don't talk too late.
Go to sleep on time.
Fine.
Ling'er, it's cold outside.
Take Wan'er inside, please.
OK. Rest assured.
I'll send her to bed on time.
Are you staying tonight?
Yes.
You don't have to.
Moreover, open that window more often.
Whether it should be closed or not at night,
it's up to the lady.
After all,
you have to prevent others from entering your room at night.
Must it be tonight?
I haven't stayed here for a long time.
Well, you don't want me to stay over?
Lady Drumstick is Lin Wan'er!
Then the girl beat me just now must be...
Ye Ling'er.
No wonder.
Who's Ye Ling'er?
She's the only daughter of Ye Zhong,
the Chief Guard of the capital city.
I've never heard of him.
Ye Liuyun, who is among the Four Great Masters,
is her granduncle.
She's practiced martial arts since childhood.
And she just loves to fight.
Why did she beat you?
She thought I was you!
Then why does she want to beat me?
Because she's a close friend to Wan'er.
She must have heard the rumors about you.
So she doesn't want Wan'er to marry you.
I've decided.
After tonight,
I'll visit the Fan mansion.
For what?
Fan Xian has learned to practice martial arts.
I'll challenge him
and give him a good beat.
I will make him give up the marriage.
Don't stand here. You might catch a cold.
Let me close the window for you.
Don't touch!
Will the carriage turn over?
What happened?
Is there anyone?
The heaven, earth and man exist in harmony.
Gentlemen shall not stay up for work.
It's midnight already.
Don't cause any trouble recently.
Why do you say so?
Your dad has agreed to break off the engagement.
Recently, he's been thinking about
your words.
Then he realized you're right.
Right for what?
Compared to the financial power of the Neiku,
perhaps your mom
would rather see you
with someone you love.
He said he would plead to His Majesty
to cancel the engagement,
so that you can find that Lady Drumstick.
Whatever
her status is,
he will support you
as long as you like her.
You've been quarreled over this for so long.
It's not easy for him
to admit his mistake right away.
I just said all these
on his behalf.
Well...
I've also thought about it for a long time.
What about
we keep this marriage?
What?
You're the one who wanted to break off the engagement.
Now suddenly,
you want to keep it instead.
Don't be mad!
I know
it's complicated.
What should I do? What should I do?
How about this?
I need to go out now.
I'll give you an answer tomorrow morning.
It's so late. Where are you going?
Well...
Wan'er, the water is ready.
Go and wash up.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
It's cold at night.
I'll close the window.
Why close it?
Today, didn't the doctor ask you
to open the window more often for good ventilation?
Just go and wash up.
The water will be cold after a while.
Just go!
I'll make the bed for you.
You're back.
I've left you some food.
I'll heat it up.
No need to bother.
I'm not that hungry.
It's fine.
Why did he go to bed so early today?
Another day of hard play.
Later,
I'll ask Fan Xian to find him a teacher.
He should be studying now.
That's terrific!
He's becoming wild
after running about in the city all day long.
He just told me that
today he got to know
a new friend
living in a box
and locked by chains.
He's just a kid after all.
Would you like a drumstick?
Why are you here?
If I say I'm here to deliver the night snack,
will you believe me?
You're a doctor in the day,
but a pervert at night!
That's not true! That's not true!
You misunderstood me! You!
I'm gonna kill you! Pervert!
You hit me so hard!
Can you be gentle?
Dapiguan Palm!
If you don't stop, I'll fight back!
Stop! I'm not a pervert!
You can ask Wan'er if you don't believe me.
You are good!
You're so violent!
Wait for me here.
Yes.
She started it!
I brought it for you.
Does it hurt?
I hardly hit her!
Are you
having a date?
A princess and a doctor
who are not afraid of worldly prejudice
get together despite the difference of their statuses.
It's just like
the stories.
What kind of stories
do you usually read?
You're good at martial arts.
The palm technique
you used
right here
is really smart!
Which one?
This one! This one!
You flatter me.
Your palm techniques are actually marvelous.
What I used is called Dapiguan Palm!
Fine. Fine.
I lost to you because I'm lame.
It doesn't mean the martial arts
handed down by my family are lame.
Sure. Sure.
If you didn't step on that,
I would never defeat you.
That's not the case.
I've thought about it.
You led me here
deliberately
just now.
I won't deny my loss.
No need to comfort me.
You've got another move.
What's this called?
Like this!
Well.
I haven't named it yet.
It's just a small trick! See?
Awesome! Awesome!
Also! Also!
You've got another move.
Right, Wan'er!
You didn't see it.
He's got a really awesome move!
Can you repeat...
Sorry.
I'm just too obsessed.
You two should talk in private.
I'll see myself out.
I won't let anyone get close!
Just talk.
I finally find you.
What for?
I don't know.
I just want to see you.
Really?
Really!
Since we met last time
in the Qing Temple,
The happiest thing I feel
is when I dream every day.
Because I can see you
in my dreams.
I was scared
every time I woke up.
I was scared that
we could only meet each other once.
I was afraid that
I could never see you again.
Now it's all right!
I've found you!
I feel so relived after finding you.
You're really a good talker.
It must be a skill cultivated
through dealing with women all the time.
Is there any misunderstanding
between us?
I don't think so.
You said you were the servant of Guo Baokun.
I've sent Ling'er to ask him.
Guo Baokun has stopped using
a servant for a long time.
I see.
You went to Guo Baokun to...
Don't move!
...inquire about me?
How rude and presumptuous of you
to break into my boudoir at night!
I've given you a hit in the day.
Don't move!
If you really don't want to see me,
you'll take out the dagger
when the other girl was here.
This is an imperial residence.
If you really get caught,
you'll be sentenced to death.
So you worry...
You...
I've known you after all,
so I don't want to see you die.
But
I don't want to hear
your sweet talks, either.
You really think
I am
frivolous?
Just leave.
Listen.
The window needs to be opened for good ventilation.
What are you doing?
But it's cold at night.
-You'd better close it. -You...
I ask you to leave. Don't you understand?
Put it down! Put it down!
Leave!
Well...
Just leave!
Calm down!
I'll leaving now!
I agree to leave,
not because I admit being dissolute.
I'm afraid that you might hurt yourself.
But every word
I just said
is from the bottom of my heart.
I never mean to show disrespect.
Wait!
Who on earth are you?
What's your name?
I'm Fan Xian.
Who do you think I am?
How dare you humiliate me like this?
I'm really Fan Xian!
You know I'm engaged to him,
so you said his name on purpose
to tease me.
It's not true.
I'm Fan Xian.
Fan Xian is me.
I've been called Fan Xian
for so many years.
I'm Fan Xian for real!
Vulgar as he is,
I've already seen him.
Actually, you pointed him to me
on the poetry gathering.
I have my reasons.
I'll explain to you later.
How is Fan Xian a vulgar man?
He beat people on the streets.
He's arrogant and impolite.
Everyone knows about that.
If you want to know a man,
you need to meet him in person.
You can't believe the rumors.
What about fooling around
with the singing girl on the carriage?
I've never done that.
Then you can't be Fan Xian.
You're misled by rumors.
I've seen it with my own eyes.
I remember.
Fan Sizhe was on that carriage.
I was not there.
You've misunderstood me.
Stop justifying yourself!
Listen!
If you continue to be disrespectful,
I can really hurt myself.
Ruoruo came with me in the day.
If I'm not Fan Xian,
how would Ruoruo
take a strange man
to see her future sister-in-law?
You've lived in the capital city for a long time.
You should know what kind of a person Ruoruo is.
She won't be so rude.
You...
How can you believe me?
Write down that poem.
Lady Ye, why are you standing here?
I...
I'm appreciating the beauty of the night.
I did hear
noise upstairs.
I was practicing martial arts upstairs.
I might have made some noise.
Princess is sick and weak.
Why would you practice martial arts
in front of her?
I'll check her up.
Wan'er is asleep.
Even if she is,
I'm responsible for checking her up.
Lady Ye, why do you stop me?
You can't go inside!
It's really you!
Many people know this poem.
Why are you sure it's me?
Indeed! Many people know this poem,
but only one person
writes so ugly.
Li Hongcheng gave it to me.
Do you believe me now?
How can you be...
No need to go inside!
Wan'er is really asleep!
Get out of the way!
You really don't have to check her up!
I told you she's asleep!
In the river of history,
time goes round and round.
Memories about the former and present lives
join each other in an endless way.
In the long drunken Milky Way,
one season follows another in a flash,
and the wild geese are flying south.
I just can't give up
to be with you for my whole life.
I have been hovering in the dreams
for hundreds and thousands of times.
I can't even say a word when I watch the flowers falling.
Year after year in the wandering,
I count the remaining years.
Even though we can't meet each other anymore,
even though we have ended up the destiny,
I never feel regretful.
In such a chaotic world,
I still miss you as ever.
I can't fall asleep under the moon.
With a gentle heart,
I cherish our remaining years.
Even though we have to go through
all the hardships along the journey,
you always stay by my side,
watching the falling flowers, speechlessly.
Year after year in the wandering,
I count the remaining years.
Even though we can't meet each other anymore,
even though we end up the destiny,
I never feel regretful.
In such a chaotic world,
I still miss you as ever.
I can't fall asleep under the moon.
With a gentle heart,
I cherish our remaining years.
Even though we have to go through
all the hardships along the journey,
you always stay by my side...